★制作软件：                           ★
★生肉啃食机:Raw-subtitle-nibble-machine★
★Srt合并盒子:SrtMergeBox              ★
https://github.com/xinghuo4096/Raw-subtitle-nibble-machine
https://github.com/xinghuo4096/SrtMergeBox
我真的需要...
I really need to...
憋住。
Hold it.
别看！
Don't look!
我爱你。
I love you.
你不必说回来。
You don't have to say it back.
对不起，我只是...
I'm sorry.I just...
我爱你。
I love you.
♪ 我是他妈的模特。
♪ I been fuckin' models.
♪ 我整晚都在吹瓶。
♪ I been poppin' bottles all night.
♪ 石窟里的花花公子。
♪ playboy in the grotto.
♪ 涂在脸上，男孩 ♪。
♪ put it on your face, boy ♪.
苏菲：他们并不像在互联网上看到的那样虚无主义。
Sophie: They're not as nihilistic
as they look on the Internet.
这就是，就像，他们希望你怎么想。
That's just, like, what they want you to think.
所以，大卫认为你是儿时的朋友。
So, David thinks you're a childhood friend.
嗯，嗯，是的，他实际上是，嗯，
Mmm-hmm.Yeah, he actually was, um,
我的学龄前男友。
my preschool boyfriend.
当然，在我意识到自己是一条汹涌的堤坝之前。
Of course, before I realized that I was a raging dyke.
哇。
Wow.
他们看起来都那么令人印象深刻。
They all look so impressive.
你令人印象深刻。
You're impressive.
好，当然。
Yeah, sure.
我是认真的。
I'm serious.
乔丹会被你迷住的。
Jordan is going to be obsessed with you.
所以...
So...
♪ 我觉得爸爸他妈的。
♪ I feel daddy as fuck.
♪ 在一辆粉红色的卡车里鞭打，爸爸他妈的。
♪ whippin' in a pink truck, daddy as fuck.
♪ 他想进入我的内心。
♪ he wanna get in my guts.
♪ 舔我的阴蒂，直到我发疯，爸爸他妈的......
♪ lickin' my clit 'til I nut, daddy as fuck....
那是谁？
Who is that?
我妈。
My mom.
♪ 哦，爸爸他妈的我觉得爸爸他妈的。
♪ Ooh, daddy as fuck I feel daddy as fuck.
你这个小怪胎。
You little freak.
我是……我不是。我只是……
I'm...I'm not.I just...
她会没事的，好吗？
She's gonna be fine, all right?
紧张没关系。
It's okay to be nervous.
这是乐趣的一部分。
That's part of the fun.
♪ 爸爸他妈的我觉得，我觉得......
♪ Daddy as fuck I feel, I feel....
♪ 哦，爸爸他妈的我觉得爸爸他妈的。
♪ Ooh, daddy as fuck I feel daddy as fuck.
♪ 爸爸他妈的我觉得爸爸他妈的。
♪ daddy as fuck I feel daddy as fuck.
♪ 我感觉，我感觉，我感觉。
♪ I feel, I feel, I feel.
♪ 来操我，我好色，哈哈！♪。
♪ Come fuck me, I'm horny, haha!♪.
呃，这该死的窗户。
Ugh, this fucking window.
会很有趣的！
It's gonna be so fun!
你来了？
You coming?
是的。嗯...
Yeah.Um...
我把东西忘在车里了。
I forgot something in the car.
好的...
Okay...
不要花太长时间。
Don't take too long.
你的游戏。
Your game.
我的天啊！
Oh, my god!
苏菲：惊喜，婊子们！
Sophie: Surprise, bitches!
我的天啊！
Oh, my god!
你他妈的婊子！
You fucking whore!
大卫：什么鬼？是苏菲。
David: What the fuck?It's Sophie.
苏菲：婊子！哦……
Sophie: Bitch!Oh...
她在这里做什么？
What is she doing here?
我不知道。爱丽丝：哦，哦……
I don't know.Alice: Oh, oh...
你好！
Hello!
苏菲：你让我湿透了，你这个坏小女孩。
Sophie: You got me soaking wet, you bad little girl.
爱丽丝：过来…… 格雷格：哇，小子！
Alice: Come here...Greg: Whoo, boy!
嘿，我赢了吗？
Hey, did I win?
是的，格雷格。
Yes, Greg.
我告诉过你们，我的肺真的很大！
I told you guys.I got really big lungs!
大卫：我知道。
David: I know.
爱丽丝：哦，天哪。
Alice: Oh, my god.
我不敢相信你在这里，就像，上次我见到你时，你
在地铁上被烧焦了，像只小鬣狗一样尿在地板上。
I can't believe you're here, like,
我不敢相信你在这里，就像，上次我见到你时，你
在地铁上被烧焦了，像只小鬣狗一样尿在地板上。
last time I saw you,
我不敢相信你在这里，就像，上次我见到你时，你
在地铁上被烧焦了，像只小鬣狗一样尿在地板上。
you were coked out on the subway,
我不敢相信你在这里，就像，上次我见到你时，你
在地铁上被烧焦了，像只小鬣狗一样尿在地板上。
pissing on the floor like a little hyena.
我以为你是纽约大学的学生。
I thought you were an nyu student.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
这就是为什么我们不再放出母鸡怪物了。
And that is why we do not let the henny monster out anymore.
不，不！
No, no!
好吧，但是，说真的，你好吗？
Okay, but, seriously, how are you?
我很好。是的。是吗？
I'm good.Yeah.Yeah?
是的，我真的很好。很好。很好。
Yeah, i'm, like, really good.Good.Good.
你看起来真好。
You look so good.
我想你！我也想你。
I miss you!I miss you too.
另外，我不得不说，喜欢播客。
Also, I have to say, love the podcast.
好的，我们有一个吊舱的粉丝。
Okay, we have a fan of the pod.
我们喜欢播客。
We love the podcast.
爱丽丝：豆荚的粉丝。
Alice: A fan of the pod.
哦，我的上帝！很高兴见到你！
Oh, my god!It's so good to see you!
我不敢相信你在这里！就像，什么？
I can't believe that you're here!It's, like, what?
嗨，嗨，我是艾玛。嗨。
Hi.Hi, I'm Emma.Hi.
哦，我的上帝。我很抱歉。
Oh, my god.I'm so sorry.
那对我太粗鲁了。我是爱丽丝。
That was so rude of me.I'm Alice.
你们，这是蜜蜂。
You guys, this is bee.
蜜蜂，这是每个人。
Bee, this is everyone.
那是大卫，
That's David, my best friend
我在全世界最好的朋友。
in the whole, whole, whole wide world.
那是艾玛。
That's Emma.
那是乔丹，还有……
That's Jordan, and...
“好！我是格雷格。
'Sup!I'm Greg.
“苏菲，玩家！我是索菲。
'Sup, player!I'm Sophie.
哦！
Oh!
哇，你是苏菲？
Whoa.You're Sophie?
真的很高兴你能成功，索夫。
Real nice of you to make it, soph.
哦，辣的，辣的，乔丹。
Ooh, spicy, spicy, Jordan.
那应该是什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
就意味着我们都来过这里，
Jordan: Just means that we have all been here
没有人知道你会来。
and nobody had any fucking clue that you were coming.
更不用说暴风雨开始前一个小时，所以...
Let alone, an hour before
the storm is supposed to start, so...
什么？我完全告诉过你们
What?I totally told you guys
我来了。
that I was coming.
我给你发了短信。
And I texted you.
在群聊中？是的。
In the group chat?Yeah.
不，你没有。无论如何，
No, you didn't.Whatever,
你们知道我对文字没用，对吧？
you guys know that i'm useless with text, right?
另外，我们本来打算昨天来的，但
是蜜蜂被安排去上班，所以...
Also, we meant to come up yesterday,
另外，我们本来打算昨天来的，但
是蜜蜂被安排去上班，所以...
but then bee got scheduled for a shift at work, so...
哦，你在哪里工作？
Oh, where do you work?
Gamehut.Emma：哦，很好。
Gamehut.Emma: Oh, nice.
爱丽丝：你们为什么这么奇怪？
Alice: Why are you guys being so weird?
你是在说我吗？
Are you talking about me?
你拿那香槟做什么？爱丽丝：伙计们！
What are you doing with that champagne?Alice: Guys!
你知道你不应该碰我爸爸的屎。
You know you're not supposed to touch my dad's shit.
苏菲来了。好的，我是苏菲。
Sophie is here.Okay, it's Sophie.
这是千百年来一次的目击事件。
It's a once in a millennium sighting.
我们正在这样做。大卫：不。
We're doing it.David: No.
是的，请。
Yes, come on.
谁想要弹出它？格雷格：我会做的。
Who wants to pop it?Greg: I'll do it.
格雷格，你会帮我弹出它吗？是的，我会弹出它。
Greg, you'll help me pop it?Yeah, I'll pop it.
好的。是的。
Okay.Yeah.
蜜蜂：我，嗯……
Bee: I, um...
我带来了一些东西。
I brought something.
哦！什么，呃……它是什么？
Oh!What, uh...what is it?
这是，呃，西葫芦。面包。
It's, uh, zucchini.A bread.
这是西葫芦面包。大卫：谢谢。
It's zucchini bread.David: Thank you.
嗯。
Yum.
嘿，书呆子。 艾玛：这很甜蜜。
Hey, nerds.Emma: That's sweet.
哦，我的上帝！哦，我的上帝！
Oh, my, god!Oh, my god!
你是怎么做到的？
How did you do that?
你看到了吗？好吧。
Did you see that?All right.
没那么酷。那太疯狂了。
It's not that cool.That was crazy.
爱丽丝：哦，天哪！
Alice: Oh, my god!
艾玛：哇。哇。
Emma: Wow.Wow.
那太恶心了。我不敢相信我们没有录下来。
That was so sick.I can't believe we didn't video that.
把我爸爸的廓尔喀剑给我。
Give me my dad's Gurkha sword.
给我那个。给你，伙计。
Gimme that.Here, man.
操，太好了。我刚在墙上找到的。
Fuck, that was so good.I just found it on the wall.
是的，不要从我的墙上抓屎。
Yeah, don't grab shit off my wall.
哇！呃，小心倒酒，
Whoa!Eh, careful with that pour,
狗屎贵。
the shits expensive.
好的，好的。我们走了。我们走了。
All right, all right.There we go.There we go.
谢谢。真令人印象深刻。
Thanks.Really impressive.
大卫：倒得不错。
David: Nice pouring.
Soph，你想要吗？我很清醒。
Soph, you want?I'm sober.
耶！不，谢谢。
Yay!No, thanks.
恭喜。
Congrats.
格雷格：干杯。艾玛：干杯。
Greg: Cheers.Emma: Cheers.
格雷格：飓风！
Greg: To hurricanes!
乔丹：参加飓风派对！
Jordan: To hurricane parties!
格雷格：是的。乔丹：飓风。
Greg: Yeah.Jordan: To hurricanes.
到飓风。
To hurricanes.
乔丹：深。
Jordan: Deep.
小伙伴们开始啦！
Guys it's starting!
晚会时间！
Party time!
开始。
Starting.
妈的。
Shit.Fuck.
好吧，麦克斯怎么了？
Okay, what's going on with Max?
没什么。他在哪里？
Nothing.Where is he?
他只是在休息，他会回来的。
He's just taking a break.He'll be back.
这意味着什么？
What does that mean?
这就是你的全部，混蛋！
Is that all you got, motherfucker!
我们走吧！
Let's go!
嘿，混蛋！
Hey, fuckface!
我们可以谈谈吗？
Can we talk for a second?
你能敲门吗？不，这是我家。
Can you knock?No, it's my house.
当然。怎么了？
Sure.What's up?
私下里哦！
In private.Oh!
当然。
Sure.
对不起，他会学习的。
I'm sorry.He'll learn.
我马上就回来。
I'll be right back.
大卫：是的，这就是汤姆汉克斯在漂流时所说的。
David: Yeah, that's what Tom Hanks said in castaway.
她其实真的很可爱。
She's actually really cute.
就像学校射击游戏一样。
In like a school shooter type of way.
“给你带来了西葫芦面包，戴夫。”
"Brought you zucchini bread, Dave."
她是我的。放手。
She's mine.Hands off.
乔丹：嘿。
Jordan: Hey.
哦，嗨……我……
Oh, hi...I...
呃，我只是……不，不，我知道。
Uh, I was just...No, no, I know.
很漂亮，房子。
It's beautiful.The house.
索菲的父母有一个更大的。
Sophie's parents have one that's even bigger.
小心点，好吗？
Just be careful, okay?
和苏菲一起……只是……
With Sophie.Just...
当心。
Be careful.
好的。
Okay.
但他，就像，不热。你明白我的意思吗？
But he's, like, not hot.You know what I mean?
他就像，就像，你妈妈会说，“哦，他很性感。”
He's like, like, your mom
would be like, "ooh, he's hot."
不是你妈妈，我是说一般的妈妈。
Not your mom, I mean moms in general.
已经结婚 10 到 15 年的妈妈们
，他们看到，比如，他走出了星巴克……
Moms that have been married
已经结婚 10 到 15 年的妈妈们
，他们看到，比如，他走出了星巴克……
for like 10, 15 years and they see, like,
已经结婚 10 到 15 年的妈妈们
，他们看到，比如，他走出了星巴克……
him going out of a Starbucks...
爱丽丝必须在不告诉任何人的情况下带人。
Alice got to bring someone without telling anyone.
所以你确实阅读了聊天记录。
So you do read the chat.
为什么大家都对聊天如此着迷？
Why is everyone so obsessed with the chat?
现在，你在这里。我在这里，我们在一起，对吧？
Now, you're here.I'm here, we're here together, right?
为什么我们担心聊天？
Why are we worrying about the chat?
当我们只能活在当下。
When we can just live in the moment.
是的，这是因为你去了康复中心，而且你没有吸毒。
Yeah, it's 'cause you went to rehab
and you're not on drugs.
所以，就像，一切都像，“哦，为
什么我们不都冷静点，伙计？”
So, like, everything is like,
所以，就像，一切都像，“哦，为
什么我们不都冷静点，伙计？”
"ooh, why don't we just all be cool, man?"
你对格雷格有什么小问题吗？
You have a little problem with Greg?
伐木工。
The lumberjack.
这是一个新的豆荚。
It's a new pod.
我还不习惯吸气。
I'm not used to the inhaling yet.
40岁的他算什么？
What is he, like, 40?
我不知道。我想爱丽丝找到了他
I don't know.I think Alice found him
在火种，或一些狗屎。
on tinder, or some shit.
显然，他在阿富汗。
Apparently, he was in Afghanistan.
我想他在军队里，或者什么狗屎，所以...
I think he was in the army, or some shit, so...
嗯，这很热。
Well, that's hot.
他不是……他不是，就像，那么热。
He's not...He's not, like, that hot.
你不必认为他有魅力，
You don't have to think he's attractive,
只有爱丽丝必须认为他有魅力。
only Alice has to think that he's attractive.
就像，我觉得，就像，我比那更有吸引力。
Like, I feel, like,
I'm more attractive than that.
你知道吗？当然。
You do?Absolutely.
您要带来哪些功能？
And what are the features
that you're bringing to the table?
好吧，我只是看起来像我他妈的。
Well, I just look like I fuck.
你知道我的意思吗？嗯。
You know what I mean?Mmm.
我看起来像我......我他妈的。
I look like I...I fuck.
这就是我喜欢在那里表现出来的氛围。
And that's the vibe I like to put out there.
是的，不，呃，是的，
Yeah.No, uh, yeah,
他，他真的很帅。随便。
he's, he's really handsome.Whatever.
我的意思是，我们不必一直谈论它。
I mean, we don't have to talk about it all the time.
你的脸怎么了？
What the fuck happened to your face?
他妈的麦克斯
Fucking Max.
麦克斯做到了？是的，他妈的麦克斯，真的。
Max did that?Yes, fucking Max, really.
好吗？我站在外面
Okay?I was standing outside
他只是跑到我面前打了我的眼睛。
and he just ran up to me and punched me in the eye.
刚刚跑到你身边？他就跑了。
Just ran up to you?He just did.
看它。他只是来找你做的，对吧？
Look at it.He just came up to you and did that, huh?
我认为它...实际上认为它看起来
I think it...Actually think it looks
不过，有点像毒品。你不觉得吗？
kind of dope, though.Don't you think?
天越来越黑了
It's getting fucking darker.
我看起来像一个，像个战士。对吧？
I look like a, like a warrior.Right?
就像，有点……有点酷。
Like, it's kind of...It's kind of cool.
比如，有点热。
Like, it's kind of hot.
就像，
Like, if you saw me coming out of a 7-Eleven,
11 出来，
you'd be like...
嗯...
Um...
所以你有机会，呃，和我父母谈谈吗？
So have you had a chance to, uh,
talk to my parents at all?
你他妈在这儿干什么，苏？
What the fuck are you doing here, soph?
我很想念你。
I missed you.
我们都知道那是谎言。
We both know that's a lie.
从来没有人想念我。
Nobody's ever missed me.
啊，不！拜托，不！
Ugh, no!Please, no!
哦，我的上帝，你能把它关掉吗？
Ugh, my god, can you turn that off?
这让我很沮丧。
It's bumming me out.
是的。你是对的。你是对的。
Yeah.You're right.You're right.
嘿，伙计们，我可以...我可以上 Wi-Fi 吗？
Hey, guys, can I...Can I get on the Wi-Fi?
哦，天哪，我永远记不住密码。
Oh, god, I can never remember the password.
这就像一个真正好的密码。
It's, like, an actually good password.
乔丹：我会转过来的。你的邮箱是什么？
Jordan: I'll transfer it.What's your email?
蜜蜂：呃……什么？
Bee: Uh...what?
你的电子邮箱是什么？
What is your email?
嘿...
Hey...
对不起，我的服务中断了，
I'm sorry.My service went out,
但我现在正在使用 Wi-Fi。
but I am on a Wi-Fi now.
所以，这很好。
So, that's good.
Greg：我100%想做一个
tiktok。你们都可以。
Greg: I 100% wanna do a tiktok.All of you can do it.
好的。你知道吗？是哪一个？
Okay.Do you know this?Which one is it?
格雷格：我不知道我在做什么。
Greg: I don't know what I'm doing.
爱丽丝：跟着……我们会看的……
Alice: Follow...We'll watch it...
你会抓住它的。是的。
You'll catch it.Yeah.
好了，准备好了，三，二……
Okay, ready, three, two...
艾玛：跟上，跟上。
Emma: Keep up, keep up.
乔丹：去吧！艾玛：看看你。
Jordan: Go!Emma: Look at you.
我们到最后了吗？
Are we at the last part?
乔丹：那很好。那很好。好的。
Jordan: That was good.That was good.Okay.
格雷格有点流氓，但我们正在检查动作。
Greg went a little rogue but we're checking the moves.
爱丽丝：不，你没有。再一次，再一次，再一次。
Alice: No, you didn't.Again, again, again.
艾玛：最后你会这样。
Emma: At the end you go like this.
爱丽丝：准备好了吗？准备好。你还好吗？
Alice: Ready?Get ready.You okay?
乔丹：我们应该，只是发布它。
Jordan: We should just, just post it.
爱丽丝：非常好。
Alice: It's very good.
乔丹：我准备好了。再来一次！
Jordan: I'm ready for the flow.One more time!
三、二、一，走！
Three, two, one, go!
你想喝一杯吗？
Do you want a drink?
你需要什么吗？
Do you want something?
给你，我们去！
Here you go.There we go!
她过得很好。
She's having a good time.
我们走吧！
Let's go!
是啊！哦，我的上帝。
Yeah!Oh, my god.
好吧，婊子。
Okay, bitch.
爱丽丝：我做的很咸。
Alice: I make it very salty.
这是令人难以置信的咸。
It's incredibly salty.
艾玛：这是你的第一次恋爱吗？
Emma: Is this your first relationship?
呃，没有。
Uh, no.
你只是，有点，给人一种氛围。
You just, kind of, give that vibe.
还不错。Bee：是的。
Not in a bad way.Bee: Yeah.
你们在一起多久了？
How long have you guys been together?
哦，呃，六周。
Oh, uh, six weeks.
不错。哇。
Nice.Wow.
和苏菲在一起六周。
Six weeks with Sophie.
爱丽丝。以一种好的方式，这很好。
Alice.In a good way, that's good.
你是莫斯科人吗？
Are you from Moscow?
蜜蜂：不，哦。
Bee: No.Oh.
蜜蜂：为什么？
Bee: Why?
日瓦戈医生是我最喜欢的电影。
Doctor Zhivago is my favorite film.
爱丽丝：呃，我的上帝，这场风暴是怎么回事？
Alice: Ugh, my god,
what is going on with this storm?
我，就像，下定决心。
I'm, like, make up your mind.
我想让它开始，就像，再次倾盆
大雨，这样我们就可以疯了。
I want it to start, like, pouring again
我想让它开始，就像，再次倾盆
大雨，这样我们就可以疯了。
so that we can go fucking crazy.
哦，你知道里面有杂草，对吧？
Oh, you know that has weed in it, right?
不是很多，我只是想让你知道。
Not a lot, I just wanted to let you know.
只是不想让你去城里然后...
Just didn't want you to go to town and then...
艾玛：是的。爱丽丝：你明白我的意思吗？
Emma: Yeah.Alice: You know what I mean?
哦，我们得到了很多喜欢。
Ooh, we're getting a lot of likes.
所有人：♪我很聪明。
All: ♪ I'm smart.
♪ 我很坚强。
♪ I'm strong.
♪ 无论发生什么，我都准备好了！
♪ I'm ready for whatever comes along!.
♪ 我有好朋友。
♪ I've got good friends.
♪ 我们会一直坚持到最后。
♪ we'll stick together to the end.
♪ 嘿，我可以回答。
♪ Hey, I can be the answer.
♪ 当鞋面起舞时，我已经准备好跳舞了。
♪ I'm ready to dance when the vamp up.
♪ 当我打到那个倾角时，拿上你的相机。
♪ and when I hit that dip get your camera.
♪ 你可以看出我从宠爱开始就是那个婊子。
♪ you could see I been that bitch since the pamper.
♪ 而且我就是那个年轻的姐姐，灯塔。
♪ and that I am that young sis, the beacon.
♪ 想要竞争的婊子和。
♪ the bitch who wants to compete and.
♪ 我可以用窥视来吓坏那个泵。
♪ I can freak a fit that pump with the peep and.
♪ 你知道你的婊子在她介入后会变成什么样子。
♪ you know what your bitch become when her weave in.
♪ 我只想喝一口。
♪ I just wanna sip that punch.
噢！噢！什么鬼？
ow!Ow!What the fuck?
♪ 与来自巴黎的婊子一起踢它。
♪ Kick it with your bitch who come from parisian.
♪ 她知道我从哪里得到我的，以及季节。
♪ she know where I get mine from, and the season.
大卫！哇！什么鬼？
David!Ow!What the fuck?
我的天啊！
Oh, my god!
♪ 我猜那婊子快被吃掉了。
♪ I guess that cunt gettin' eaten.
你是内奸吗？
are you being an incel?
我被烧焦了，我咬了她。
I'm coked up and I bit her.
♪ 我是在212 on uptown 一个。
♪ I was in the 212 on the uptown a.
♪ 兄弟们，你知道发生了什么事吗？
♪ nigga, you know what's up or don't you?.
♪ 对谁让你说我是个粗鲁的婊子，兄弟们。
♪ Word to who made ya I'm a rude bitch, nigga.
♪ 你是由什么组成的？
♪ what are you made up of?.
♪ 我是吃你的饭了，嘘。
♪ I'm a eat your food up, boo.
♪ 我看起来是对的，兄弟们打赌你确实想他妈的。
♪ I'm a look right, nigga bet you do want to fuck.
♪ 黑鬼更好，哦，快跑。
♪ niggas better, ohh-run-run.
♪ 你可能会被枪杀，伙计。
♪ you could get shot, homie.
♪ 如果你确实想举起枪来。
♪ if you do want to put your guns up.
♪ 告诉你的船员不要在我面前流氓，兄弟们。
♪ tell your crew don't front I'm a hoodlum, nigga.
打扰一下。
excuse me.
♪ 婊子，我也快要炸了。
♪ Bitch, I'm 'bout to blew up too.
♪ 我是今天的那个我是新的狗屎嘘。
♪ I'm the one today I'm the new shit boo.
你也是，嗯...
so did you, um...
你在美国上过大学吗，或者，嗯...
Did you go to college here in the states, or, um...
是的，在这里......我的意思是，在犹他州。
Yeah, here...I, I mean, in Utah state.
苏菲：你需要冷静一下。
Sophie: You need to chill out.
大卫：我猜。
David: I guess.
不，我是认真的，你需要...
No, I'm serious, you need to...
你需要冷静下来。
You need to chill out.
我只是真的出汗了，我需要给自己补充水分。
I'm just really sweaty and I need to hydrate myself.
好的？
Okay?
你应该注意你的女孩。
You should watch your girl.
看起来她和乔丹玩得很开心。
Looks like she's having fun with Jordan.
♪ 当我出现时你会做什么？
♪ What you gon' do when I appear?.
♪ 当我首映？
♪ When I premiere?.
♪ 婊子，你的生命即将结束。
♪ Bitch, the end of your lives are near.
♪ 这狗屎是我的，我的！
♪ this shit been mine, mine!.
♪ 婊子，我在 212。
♪ Bitch, I'm in the 212.
♪ 第五个竖起的黑鬼是 21 动物园。
♪ with the fifth cocked nigga it's the 21 zoo.
♪ 当你的笨蛋喷了的时候，你他妈的会做什么？
♪ fuck you gon' do when your goon sprayed up?.
♪ 打赌他的婊子不会得到他，打赌你不会做太多事情。
♪ Bet his bitch won't get him betcha you won't do much.
♪ 看看你是否想破产。
♪ see even if you do want to bust.
♪ 你的婊子也会让你剪掉并抚摸你的船员。
♪ your bitch'll get you cut and touch your crew up too.
♪ 流行音乐，你在玩你的黄油。
♪ pop, you playin' with your butter.
♪ 就像你的嘘声也不会真正开枪。
♪ like your boo won't true cock the gun too.
♪ 你在哪里吃 poom，嗯。
♪ where you do eat poom, hun.
♪ 我他妈的和你的可爱 q 在一起。
♪ I'm fuckin' with your cutie q.
♪ 你的鸡巴是什么样的，兄弟你喜欢什么？
♪ what's your dick like, homie what are you into?.
♪ 什么是奔跑老兄？你在哪里醒来？
♪ What's the run dude?Where do you wake up?.
♪ 告诉你的婊子继续讨厌......♪. 沉默！
♪ Tell your bitch keep hatin'...♪.
Silence!
乔丹：什么？停下！
Jordan: What?Stop!
谁想玩身体身体？
Who wants to play bodies bodies bodies?
大卫：啊，操！艾玛：是的！
David: Ah, fuck!Emma: Yes!
所以，
Sophie: So, if you draw the piece of paper
的那张纸，
that has the "x" on it,
你就是凶手。
you are the murderer.
你必须保守秘密。
And you have to keep it a secret.
伙计们，每次我们玩这个我都会感到压力很大。
Guys, I get so stressed out every time we play this.
总有人哭到最后。
Someone always ends up crying.
爱丽丝：你总是哭到最后。
Alice: You always end up crying.
好吧，我可以很容易地了解我的情绪。
Okay, I can access my emotions easily.
爱丽丝：非常容易。
Alice: Very incredibly easily.
她是演员，总是先哭。
She's an actress, she always cries first.
我只是说，这游戏变得非常丑陋。
I'm just saying, this game gets very ugly.
哦，我的上帝，不，它没有。
Oh, my god, no, it does not.
当她难看的哭声时，它会变得难看。
It gets ugly when she ugly cries.
艾玛：从字面上看，每次我们玩
的时候，人们都会开始打架。
Emma: Literally, every single time we play,
艾玛：从字面上看，每次我们玩
的时候，人们都会开始打架。
people start fighting.
大卫：是的，嗯，这就是有趣的原因，艾玛。
David: Yeah, well, that's what makes it fun, Emma.
麦克斯在哪里？
Where's Max?
他没有回复我的短信。
He's not responding to my texts.
哦，耶稣...
Oh, Jesus...
那么，你怎么玩？
So, how do you play?
苏菲：所以，我马上就要开灯了。
Sophie: So, I'm gonna hit the lights in a second.
如果你是凶手，
And if you are the murderer,
你必须偷偷摸摸杀了人，
you have to sneak around and kill someone
比如摸他们的背。
by, like, touching them on the back.
然后，其他人都必须避免被杀。
And then, everyone else has to avoid being killed.
然后，如果你被杀了，你必须倒下，假装你已经死了。
And then, if you are killed,
you have to fall down and pretend you're dead.
爱丽丝：像这样。
Alice: Like this.
格雷格：酷。
Greg: Cool.
嘿，呃……爱丽丝，你想……
Hey, uh...Alice, do you wanna...
什么？ 大卫：你想...
What?David: Do you wanna...
你知道。哦！对不起，我得走了。
You know.Oh!Excuse me, I have to go.
这是紧急情况。
It's an emergency.
打扰一下。
Excuse me.
乔丹：最重要的部分是，如果你遇到一个尸
体，你必须大喊，“尸体，尸体，尸体”。
Jordan: The most important part
乔丹：最重要的部分是，如果你遇到一个尸
体，你必须大喊，“尸体，尸体，尸体”。
is if you do come across a body,
乔丹：最重要的部分是，如果你遇到一个尸
体，你必须大喊，“尸体，尸体，尸体”。
you have to yell, "bodies, bodies, bodies."
然后，一旦发生这种情况，我们将重新打开
所有灯，然后我们将尝试找出是谁做的。
And then, once that happens,
然后，一旦发生这种情况，我们将重新打开
所有灯，然后我们将尝试找出是谁做的。
we'll turn all the lights back on
然后，一旦发生这种情况，我们将重新打开
所有灯，然后我们将尝试找出是谁做的。
and then we'll try to figure out who did it.
你能拿着这个吗？
Could you hold this?
格雷格碰过那个吗？
Did Greg touch that?
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
你对格雷格太牛逼了。
You're being such a dick about Greg.
拿着这个。
Just hold this.
大卫...
David...
什么？我，呃……
What?I, ugh...
好的...
Okay...
看看，到底是怎么回事？
Look, what the fuck's going on?
苏菲：到地板上来。
Sophie: Come to the floor.
来到地板上。
Come to the floor.
乔丹：让你的屁股过来，男孩。
Jordan: Get your ass over here, boy.
苏菲：好的。好的。
Sophie: Okay.All right.
乔丹：谁将获得荣誉？
Jordan: Who will do the honors?
哦...
Oh...
进去吧，走吧。
Get into it.Let's go.
乔丹：噢！
Jordan: Ow!
啊！
Ahhh!
婊子。
Bitch.
爱丽丝：你生我的气吗？
Alice: Are you mad at me?
乔丹：不。爱丽丝：好的。
Jordan: No.Alice: Okay.
蜜蜂：哇！爱丽丝：乔丹！
Bee: Ow!Alice: Jordan!
苏菲：哇。什么？这是游戏。
Sophie: Whoa.What?It's the game.
大卫：哇扎……
David: Wowza...
哦，我的上帝......哦，来吧！
Oh, my god...Oh, come on!
那是什么？蜜蜂！
What was that?Bee!
你必须打得更多。你必须放
You have to hit more.You got to put
一些肌肉进去。你必须......是的，去争取它。
some muscle into it.You gotta...Yeah, go for it.
是的。
Yeah.
来吧！
Come on!
乔丹：打他一巴掌，他活该。
Jordan: Slap him around, he deserves it.
大卫：他妈的打我！
David: Fucking hit me!
艾玛：他想要。乔丹：不，他应得的。
Emma: He wants it.Jordan: No, he deserves it.
他真的活该。做吧。
He really deserves it.Do it.
如果有人值得被打，那应该是他。
If anyone deserves to be hit, it should be him.
是的。蜜蜂：好的。
Yeah.Bee: Okay.
哦，他妈的看在这样的份上。
Oh, for fuck sake like this.
爱丽丝：哦，天哪！
Alice: Oh, my god!
乔丹：大卫！大卫。
Jordan: David!David.
看到了吗？大卫。
See?David.
你他妈是个混蛋！
You're a fucking dick!
什么？
What?
你真是个混蛋。
You are such an asshole.
我正在教她如何玩游戏。
I'm teaching her how to play the game.
爱丽丝：宝贝，停下，停下！
Alice: Baby, stop, stop!
等等，伙计们，必须有人打我。
Wait, guys, someone has to hit me.
谁要打我？
Who's gonna hit me?
乔丹：我会做的。
Jordan: I'll do it.
艾玛：噢！
Emma: Ow!
谢谢。乔丹：不客气。
Thank you.Jordan: You're welcome.
苏菲：好的！
Sophie: Okay!
我们准备好出发了吗？爱丽丝：是的，我们他妈的走吧。
Are we ready to go?Alice: Yes, let's fucking go.
大卫：是的。爱丽丝：我们玩游戏吧。
David: Yes.Alice: Let's play the game.
大卫：我的天！我完蛋了。
David: Holy shit!I'm so fucked up.
啊。
Ahh.
你准备好了吗？
You ready?
是的。
Yes.
蜜蜂：嘿。
Bee: Hey.
哦！
Oh!
苏菲：我看到白人……
Sophie: I see white man...
身体，身体，身体！
Bodies, bodies, bodies!
你们！在这里。
You guys!Over here.
不！
No!
好吧，
Jordan: All right, who tried to take advantage
谁想在黑暗中利用我的身体？
of my body in the dark?
你的愿望，宝贝。
Your wish, babe.
爱丽丝：哦，为什么，上帝？为什么？他太热了！
Alice: Oh, why, god?Why?He was so hot!
是你吗？不。
Was it you?No.
好的。那么，我们有任何提名吗？
Okay.So, do we have any nominations?
大卫：艾玛哇。
David: Emma whoa.
哇，进来很热。什么？
Wow, coming in hot.What?
为什么？是的，我认为是艾玛。
Why?Yup, I think it was Emma.
为什么你认为是我？
Why do you think it was me?
爱丽丝：是的，大卫，为什么？
Alice: Yeah, David, why?
大卫：好的，好吧，她只是同意每个人所说的一切。
David: Okay, well, she just, like,
agrees with everything that everybody is saying.
这就是她在这场比赛中的策略，
And that's her strategy in this game
而且每次都奏效。
and it works every single time.
所以，我现在就叫它。是艾玛。
So, I'm just calling it now.It's Emma.
苏菲：我们还有其他提名吗？
Sophie: Do we have any other nominations?
嗯……是的，大卫。
Um...yeah, David.
大卫：哦，来吧。这是很容易实现的目标。
David: Oh, come on.It's low hanging fruit.
我的意思是，他是投下第一块石头的人。
I mean, he who casts the first stone.
蜜蜂：伙计们，他为什么不动？
Bee: Guys, why isn't he moving?
格雷格？宝贝，起来。
Greg?Baby, get up.
你不必假装这么久。
You don't have to keep pretending for this long.
宝贝？来吧，格雷格。
Baby?Come on, Greg.
爱丽丝：格雷格……
Alice: Greg...
格雷格...
Greg...
起床。
Get up.
等待。
Wait.
格雷格？
Greg?
格雷格！
Greg!
格格，起来！
Greg, get up!
格雷格！他没有起床。
Greg!He's not getting up.
嘿，放松，这总是有效的。我知道。
Hey, relax, this always works.I know.
哦，嘿！哦，我的上帝。
Oh, hey!Oh, my god.
你真的把我吓坏了。
You really scared me with that.
艾玛：你是个小骗子，格雷格。
Emma: You're a little trickster, Greg.
乔丹：我知道，耶稣基督。
Jordan: I know, Jesus Christ.
苏菲：可爱。
Sophie: Cute.
好吧，那么……大卫呢？
Okay, so...what about David?
等等，
Alice:
也许是乔丹。
Wait, maybe it's Jordan.
当她是杀手时，她总是非常具有侵略性。
She's always really aggressive when she's the killer.
你去吧。什么？不，我不是。
There you go.What?No, I am not.
你在撒谎。
You're lying.
当你撒谎时，你的声音总是很高。
Your voice always goes really high when you lie.
不，它没有。我……它……我已经……
No, it doesn't.I...it...I've...
肯定是大卫。你为什么大喊大叫？
It's definitely David.Why are you yelling?
如果我是凶手，那就太他妈明显了，但我不是。
That would be so fucking obvious
if I were the killer, which I'm not.
戴夫，
I think you're digging yourself
我认为你是在自掘坟墓。
into a little hole here, Dave.
大卫：伙计们，耶稣基督……
David: Guys, Jesus Christ...
最好的防守是好的进攻。
The best defense is a good offense.
嘿，你闭嘴。你不应该说话。你已经死了。
Hey, you shut up.You're not supposed to talk.You're dead.
死者实际上是不应该说话的。
The dead are actually not supposed to speak.
哦，是的，你......对不起
，宝贝，你不能。这是一个规则。
Oh, yeah, you...sorry, baby, you can't.It's a rule.
哦，我的 b. 是的，不说话。收拾东西。
Oh, my b.Yeah, no talking.Pack it up.
大卫：这他妈是什么意思，格雷格？
David: What the fuck does that even mean, Greg?
这是怎么回事？
What's up?
“最好的防守就是好的进攻。”
"The best defense is a good offense."
那是什么……这是什么意思？
What does that...What does that mean?
哦，你知道，最好的防守是好的进攻。
Oh, you know, the best defense is a good offense.
什么……这到底是什么意思？
What...What does it mean, though?
嗯，嗯...
Uh, well...
它，嗯……它意味着最好的防御
It, um...it means that the best defense
是一个很好的进攻。
is a good offense.
对对对，我听到了。
Right, right, I heard you.
但是，这对你意味着什么，格雷格？就像...
But, what does it mean to you, Greg?Like...
不知道，能不能详细介绍一下？
I don't know, could you elaborate on it for us?
把它分解。
Break it down.
好，当然。
Yeah, sure.
所以，嘿，看看体育，有...
So, hey, look in sports, there's...
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
你真是个混蛋。
You are such a fucking dick.
嘿，这是一个教学时刻。
Hey, this is a teaching moment.
我懂了。
Oh, I see.
你在和我混
You're fucking with me.
不，不，
No.No,
我不是在跟你开玩笑，格雷格。
I'm not fucking with you, Greg.
我只是玩得开心。
I'm just having fun.
我们都只是玩得很​​开心。
We're all just having a good time.
对吧，伙计们？
Right, guys?
对吧，格雷格？
Right, Greg?
我们只是玩得开心。
We're just having fun.
你知道，
You know,
我想是时候让我自己去睡觉了。
I think it's time for me to put myself to bed.
乔丹：哦，来吧，格雷格。爱丽丝：格雷格，不。
Jordan: Oh, come on, Greg.Alice: Greg, no.
晚安，格雷格。
Good night, Greg.
你们孩子玩得开心。
You kids have fun.
苏菲：稍后再接你，玩家。
Sophie: Catch you later, player.
大卫：顺便说一句，我能不能把我们所有的注意力
都放在艾玛一个他妈的一句话都没说的事实上。
David: By the way,
大卫：顺便说一句，我能不能把我们所有的注意力
都放在艾玛一个他妈的一句话都没说的事实上。
can I just point all of our attention
大卫：顺便说一句，我能不能把我们所有的注意力
都放在艾玛一个他妈的一句话都没说的事实上。
to the fact that Emma hasn't said a fucking word.
爱丽丝：哇，你说得对。
Alice: Whoa, you're right.
哇，她没有！
Whoa, she hasn't!
大卫：我只是指出显而易见的。仅此而已。
David: I'm just pointing out the obvious.That's all.
看，她正在做那种吞咽的事情。
Look, she's doing that swallowing thing.
她在他妈紧张的时候总是这样！
She always does that when she's fucking nervous!
爱丽丝：哦，我的上帝！看，看！
Alice: Oh, my god!Look, look!
哦，我的上帝，你正在这样做。你正在吞下它。
Oh, my god, you're doing it.You're swallowing it.
我不是。爱丽丝：你是。
I'm not.Alice: You are.
好吧，我爱你，但是当你吞下去的时候，它
只是他妈的......就像，为什么？
Okay, I love you, but when you swallow,
好吧，我爱你，但是当你吞下去的时候，它
只是他妈的......就像，为什么？
it's just fucking...Like, why?
吞咽是正常的。
Swallowing is normal.
这是很正常的事情。大卫：是的...
It's a normal thing to do.David: Yeah...
这很不吸引人。我不知道你为什么这样做？
It's very UN-attractive.I don't know why you do it?
哦，我的上帝。这就是你们从不做爱的原因吗？
Oh, my god.Is that why you guys never have sex?
什么？爱丽丝。
What?Alice.
什么？这不是一件坏事。有些人经常做爱。
What?It's not a bad thing.Some people have sex a lot.
有些人少了。
Some people have it less.
爱丽丝，你在说什么？我们知道。
Alice, what are you talking about?We do.
我有很多。一些...
I have it a lot.Some...
你他妈的在... Sophie：哦，我的上帝。
Are you fucking...Sophie: Oh, my god.
你他妈是在背后议论我们吗？
Are you fucking talking about us behind my back?
不，是的。
No.Yes.
艾玛：不，是的。
Emma: No.Yes.
不，我不是。
No, I'm not.
我不是！我不是。
I'm not!I'm not.
我只是... 大卫：那太好了。
I just...David: That's just great.
艾玛：不，我……我们……我…
…你从来没有真正……我……
Emma: No, I...we...I...you never really...I...
我不……你总是在给我打气。
I don't...You're always gaslighting me.
“煤气灯，”闭嘴。这是一个他妈的愚蠢的词。
"Gaslight," shut up.It's a fucking dumb word.
打扰一下？
Excuse me?
Gaslight 是，就像，有史以来最过
度使用的词之一，到，就像，毁灭的地步。
Gaslight is, like, one of the most over used words ever,
Gaslight 是，就像，有史以来最过
度使用的词之一，到，就像，毁灭的地步。
to, like, the point of annihilation.
好吧，除了你阅读互联网这一事
实之外，它没有其他任何意义。
Okay, it doesn't mean anything other than the fact
好吧，除了你阅读互联网这一事
实之外，它没有其他任何意义。
that, like, you read the Internet.
或者，例如，“恭喜，你有一个
Twitter 帐户。”
Or, like, "congrats, you have a Twitter account."
呃，这太他妈的蹩脚了。
Ugh, that is so fucking lame.
大卫：“煤气灯，”克服它。
David: "Gaslight," get over it.
就像接下来会发生什么？你会称我为自恋者吗？
Like what's next?You're gonna call me a narcissist?
还是白人至上的步兵？
Or a foot soldier of, like, the white supremacy?
就像，来吧，他妈的，更原始的。
Like, come on, fucking, be more original.
苏菲：跛脚。
Sophie: Lame.
大卫：什么？我只是说，这就是我要说的，
David: What?I'm just saying, that, this is what I'm saying,
她他妈的脑子里没有其他人没有说过的想法。
she doesn't have a thought in her fucking head
that hasn't been said by anybody else.
没有什么不是预定的。
Nothing that isn't preordained.
爱丽丝：大卫，这真的很刻薄。
Alice: David, that's really mean.
看，她在哭。
Look, she's crying.
大卫：什么？
David: What?
为什么大家都这样看我？
Why is everybody looking at me like that?
这不是她真正的哭泣。
This is not her real cry.
我投票给大卫。
I vote David.
我也是。
Yeah, me too.
你他妈是认真的吗？
Are you fucking serious?
伙计们，这是艾玛。
Guys, it's Emma.
她是演员。她在演戏。
She's an actress.She's acting.
第三。
Third.
大卫：哇，真他妈的令人惊讶。
David: Wow, how fucking surprising.
是的，看看你颤抖的上唇。
Yeah, look at your quivering upper lip.
就像，我们都没有在 hedda
gabler 看到你。去你的。
Like, we all didn't see you in hedda gabler.Fuck you.
是的，是的，是的……第四。
Yeah, yeah, yup...fourth.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
去他妈的这个游戏！
Fuck this game!
爱丽丝：天哪。
Alice: Holy shit.
关系可能真的很复杂。
Relationships can be really complicated.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我很好，你确定吗？
I'm fine.Are you sure?
我很好。我 100% 很好。你确定吗，宝贝？
I'm fine.I'm 100% fine.Are you sure, baby?
是的，我们玩吧。
Yes.Let's play.
哦！
Ow!
爱丽丝：哇，好一个。
Alice: Wow, good one.
乔丹：突然间她喜欢上了比赛。
Jordan: All of a sudden she loves the game.
爱丽丝：那太疯狂了。
Alice: That was crazy.
把它给我。
Give it to me.
乔丹：该死！
Jordan: Damn!
爱丽丝：啊！哦，我的上帝！
Alice: Ah!Oh, my god!
艾玛：那是什么？
Emma: What was that?
爱丽丝：什么鬼？ 乔丹：那是灯吗？
Alice: What the fuck?Jordan: Is that the lights?
艾玛：那是什么？
Emma: What was that?
苏菲：哦，我的上帝。 艾玛：那是暴风雨造成的吗？
Sophie: Oh, my god.Emma: Was that from the storm?
苏菲：哦，我的上帝。我敢打赌那是大卫。
Sophie: Oh, my god.I bet you that it was David.
大卫！乔丹：不是大卫。来吧。
David!Jordan: It's not David.Come on.
我正在给他发短信。
I'm texting him.
大卫，你在和我们玩吗？
David, are you fucking with us?
重新打开灯。
Turn the lights back on.
你好，有人服务吗？
Hey, does anybody have service?
不！
No!
呃，等等，我的不工作了。
Ugh, wait, mine's not working.
好的，我认为 WiFi 也已关闭。
Okay, I think the WiFi is also down.
哦，我的上帝，我他妈的要杀了他。
Oh, my god, i'm gonna fucking kill him.
太棒了！大卫！
Great!David!
大卫！这真是他妈的可爱！
David!This is real fucking cute!
Soph，
Jordan: Soph, can he disable the generator from garage,
地下室或其他地方的发电机关掉吗？
or the basement, or whatever?
我不知道。
I don't know.
大卫！
David!
好吧，好吧，我要去打开断路器。
Okay, well, I'm gonna go and flip the breaker.
是在车库还是在地下室？
Is it in the garage or is it in the basement?
大卫！乔丹：索夫？
David!Jordan: Soph?
嗯，什么？ Jordan：好吧，随便。
Huh, what?Jordan: Okay, whatever.
好的，我要去拿更多的手电筒。
Okay, I'm gonna go get some more flashlights.
艾玛：我要去洗手间。
Emma: I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
浴室在哪里？
Where is a bathroom?
嗯，嗯，楼下，你右边的第一扇门。
Um, uh, downstairs, first door on your right.
蜜蜂：去那里。
Bee: Going there.
苏菲：大卫？
Sophie: David?
大卫，你在和我们玩吗？
David, are you fucking with us?
我指的是其他楼梯。
I meant the other stairs.
大卫！大卫！
David!David!
帮助！有人帮助！
Help!Somebody help!
不不不。
No, no, no.
爱丽丝：他妈的怎么了？
Alice: What the fuck happened?
哦，我的上帝！为什么会...
Oh, my god!Why would...
乔丹：检查他的脉搏。苏菲：什么鬼？
Jordan: Check his pulse.Sophie: What the fuck?
乔丹：哦，操！哦，我的上帝！
Jordan: Oh, fuck!Oh, my god!
抬起他的头！
Hold his head up!
哦，我的上帝！操！
Oh, my god!Fuck!
操！爱丽丝：他快死了吗？
Fuck!Alice: Is he dying?
抬起他的头！艾玛：来吧，宝贝，坚持住。
Hold his head up!Emma: Come on, baby, hold on.
苏菲：他的脖子怎么了？
Sophie: What the fuck happened to his neck?
我爱你，大卫。狗屎。
I love you, David.Shit.
爱丽丝：发生了什么事？
Alice: What is happening?
拉屎！
Shit!
爱丽丝：你在做什么？我打911！
Alice: What are you doing?I'm calling 911!
哦，我的上帝！你有服务吗？
Oh, my god!You have service?
操，不！你呢？
Fuck, no!Do you?
不！乔丹：操！
No!Jordan: Shit!
你要去哪里？座机！
Where are you going?Landline!
我们应该移动他的身体吗？
We should move his body?
为什么？我不知道。因为他...
Why?I don't know.Because he's...
爱丽丝：不，你不能动他。
Alice: No, you can't move him.
你看过svu吗？这是证据。
Did you watch svu?It's evidence.
什么？爱丽丝：原因！
Of what?Alice: Cause!
固定电话？不，没有连接。
Landline?No, there's no connection.
苏菲，你的钥匙呢？
Sophie, where are your keys?
你的钥匙，苏菲，它们在哪里？
Your keys, Sophie, where are they?
它们在口袋里。
They're in the pocket.
它们在她的口袋里……在哪里？他妈的救命！
They're in her pocket...Where?Fucking help!
爱丽丝：你要去哪里？
Alice: Where are you going?
我要去车上。爱丽丝：去车上？为什么？
I'm going to the car.Alice: To the car?Why?
得到一些他妈的帮助。
To get some fucking help.
等等，你有驾照吗？
Wait, do you have a license?
她不是没有驾照吗？
Doesn't she not have a license?
我不知道。我不这么认为。
I don't know.I don't think so.
爱丽丝：操！蜜蜂：他死了！
Alice: Fuck!Bee: He's dead!
你得走了！我不知道！
You have to go!I don't know!
他停止了呼吸！
He stopped breathing!
乔丹：支线！
Jordan: Branch!
爱丽丝：你必须推动油门。
Alice: You have to push the gas.
乔丹：我他妈的知道怎么开车，爱丽丝！
Jordan: I know how to fucking drive, Alice!
我看不见。 乔丹：电池没电了吗？
I can't see.Jordan: Is the battery dead?
蜜蜂：哦，不……乔丹：什么？
Bee: Oh, no...Jordan: What?
我，我想我把灯放在镜子上。
I, I think I left the light on, on the mirror.
爱丽丝：哦，耶稣基督。
Alice: Oh, Jesus Christ.
艾玛：我们他妈的该怎么办？
Emma: What the fuck are we supposed to do?
蜜蜂：等等，你的车呢？
Bee: Wait, where are your cars?
爱丽丝：我们……我们只有一辆车。
Alice: We...We only have one car.
麦克斯把我们都抱起来了，他他妈的离开了！
Max picked us all up and he fucking left!
乔丹：操，操，操！
Jordan: Fuck, fuck, fuck!
麦克斯可能随时都会到，对吧？
Max will probably be here any minute, right?
乔丹在哪里？
Where's Jordan?
她去检查发电机，我...
She went to check the generator, I...
他他妈在做什么？
What the fuck was he doing?
你在说什么？ 苏菲：他妈的他在做什么？
What are you talking about?Sophie: Fuck was he doing?
为什么他在暴风雨中在外面？
Why the fuck was he outside in the storm?
乔丹：嘿！是我，让我进去！
Jordan: Hey!It's me, let me in!
我找到了这个。
I found this.
外面的泥泞中。
Outside in the mud.
苏菲：别碰啊，停电了，安防系统还能用吗？
Sophie: Don't touch it
um, does the security system work if the power goes out?
嗯...
Um...
是的，是的，是的，确实如此。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it does.
大卫的父亲向我们解释了这一点。
David's dad explained it to us.
没有密码，任何人都无法进入。
Nobody can get in without the code.
好吧，Max 有密码。
Well, Max has the code.
所以……麦克斯不会……
So...Max wouldn't...
我只是说，就像，他他妈在哪里？
I'm just saying, like, where the fuck is he?
昨晚他就不能回来了吗？
Couldn't he have come back after last night?
爱丽丝，停下。
Alice, stop.
昨晚发生了什么？
What happened last night?
什么都没有。爱丽丝：没有。
Nothing.Alice: No.
我们做了蘑菇，
We did shrooms
马克斯告诉大家他爱上了艾玛。
and Max told everybody that he was in love with Emma.
大卫当时认为这很美，
Which David thought was beautiful in the moment,
但今天可能不是。
but maybe not today.
爱丽丝，从字面上看，这他妈的根本不重要。
Alice, that literally doesn't fucking matter at all.
格雷格在哪里？他在哪里？
Where is Greg?Where is he?
什么？乔丹：格雷格在哪里？
What?Jordan: Where is Greg?
我...
I...
他说他要去睡觉了。
He said he was going to bed.
所以我的猜测是他在睡觉。
So my guess would be that he's sleeping.
好吧，
Okay, don't you think it's a little bit strange
你不觉得他还没有醒来有点奇怪吗？
that he hasn't, like, woken up yet?
乔丹，
Jordan,
你想说什么。
what are you trying to say.
也许我们应该去看看他。
Maybe we should just go check on him.
爱丽丝：不，不，不。
Alice: No, no, no.
约旦...
Jordan...
你在做什么？乔丹……乔丹。
What are you doing?Jordan...Jordan.
你在干什么！
What are you doing!
我很安全。爱丽丝：真的吗？
I'm staying safe.Alice: Really?
因为看起来你正在抓着一把他妈的切肉刀去找我的男朋友！
Because it looks like you're grabbing
a fucking meat cleaver to go look for my boyfriend!
哇。男朋友？
Wow.Boyfriend?
这是我第一次听到你这么叫他。
That's the first time I've heard you call him that.
太疯狂了。
That's crazy.
爱丽丝：别这么贱。
Alice: Don't be such a bitch.
乔丹：爱丽丝，我真的只是在保护自己，好吗？
Jordan: Alice, I'm literally just protecting myself, okay?
让我提醒你，我们的朋友已经死了。
Let me remind you, our friend is dead.
所以，如果你能，比如，不要让局势升级......
So, if you could just, like, not escalate the situation...
我没有升级。你拿着刀
I'm not escalating.You're holding the knife
你说话的时候在移动你的手。
and you're moving your hands while you talk.
爱丽丝，你认识格雷格多久了？
Alice, how long have you known Greg?
喜欢...
Like...
长。
Long.
爱丽丝。
Alice.
啊...
Ugh...
我不知道具体要多久。
I don't know exactly how long.
我喜欢...
I...Like...
两周。
Two weeks.
乔丹：好的，呃……
Jordan: Okay, uh...
你对格雷格了解多少，爱丽丝？
What do you know about Greg, Alice?
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
乔丹：你对他了解多少？
Jordan: What do you know about him?
哦，天哪，伙计们！
Oh, my god, guys!
苏菲：哦，天哪！放松，停下！
Sophie: Oh, my god!Relax.Stop!
停！停！我知道他是个好人，好吗？
Stop!Stop!I know that he's a good person, okay?
他本质上是个好人。
He's fundamentally a good person.
他不会这样做。就像，不。
He wouldn't do this.Like, no.
你知道他的中间名吗？你知道他住在哪里吗？
Do you know his middle name?Do you know where he lives?
你知道他他妈的赚了多少钱吗？
Do you know how much fucking money he makes?
你知道他的姓吗，爱丽丝？
Do you know his last name, Alice?
我知道很多。
I know a lot.
我们的第一次约会是在……在一家酒吧。
Our first date was at...Was at a bar.
他喝了，就像，中等量......
He drank, like, a medium amount...
乔丹：好吧，爱丽丝……停下。他喜欢大自然。
Jordan: Okay, Alice...stop.He likes nature.
乔丹：他的中间名是什么？
Jordan: What is his middle name?
他是天秤座的月亮。乔丹：他住在哪里？
He's a libra moon.Jordan: Where does he live?
你不要问你的中间名是什么！
You don't ask what your middle name is!
好吧？真的很久了。Jordan：哦……操！
Okay?For a really long time.Jordan: Oh...fuck!
他是天秤座月亮。这说明了很多！
He's a libra moon.That says a lot!
他妈的！
Fuck!
格雷格！嘘！
Greg!Shh!
爱丽丝：什么？你刚才说我们在找格雷格！
Alice: What?You just said we're looking for Greg!
好吧，别他妈的，爱丽丝……
Okay, well don't fucking, Alice...
格雷格！你能进厨房吗？
Greg!Can you come into the kitchen?
我们需要你一秒钟。
We need you for a second.
闭嘴，别对我挥刀了！
Shut up.Stop waving the knife at me!
操，你让我...
Fuck.You're making me...
停。停。格雷格！
Stop.Stop.Greg!
停下来，停下来，安静点。
Stop.Just stop.Just be quiet.
停。停。
Stop.Stop.
格雷格！不要。放松。
Greg!Don't.Relax.
不要抓住我的嘴。放松。放松。放松。
Don't grab my mouth.Relax.Relax.Relax.
你在让我沉默。哦，我的上帝。
You're silencing me.Oh, my god.
滚开。好吧，停下。
Get the fuck off.Okay, stop.
爱丽丝：别再那样抓我了。
Alice: Don't grab me like that again.
她拿着刀向我冲过来。
And she came at me with a knife.
乔丹：对不起……爱丽丝：退后。
Jordan: I'm sorry...Alice: Back off.
好吧，巴克！
Okay, buck!
等等，艾玛在哪里？
Wait, where's Emma?
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
乔丹：艾玛？
Jordan: Emma?
艾玛？
Emma?
伙计们，
Guys,
也许艾玛可以做到。
maybe Emma could have done it.
她真的生大卫的气。
She was really pissed at David.
苏菲：爱丽丝，这他妈是什么？
Sophie: Alice, what the fuck?
苏菲：艾玛不会那样做。
Sophie: Emma wouldn't do that.
她被摧毁了。
She was devastated.
她有，就像，一个全面的惊恐发作。
She's having, like, a full-on panic attack.
是的，但她是一名演员。
Yeah, but she's an actress.
她在演戏，还记得海达高博吗？
She's acting.Remember hedda gabler?
好吧，不要刻薄，但她在 hedd
a gabler 方面没那么好。
Okay, not to be mean,
好吧，不要刻薄，但她在 hedd
a gabler 方面没那么好。
but she wasn't that good in hedda gabler.
这是我的房间。
This is my room.
所以打开它。
So open it.
你打开它。
You open it.
发生了什么事，“格雷格永远不会这样做？”
What happened to, "Greg would never do this?"
他不会。好吧，打开它。
He wouldn't.Okay, so open it.
我会在一秒钟内。
I will in one second.
我要去。
I'm going to.
苏菲：他不在这里。
Sophie: He's not here.
Soph，家里有枪吗？
Soph, are there any guns in the house?
枪？
Guns?
不，不可能。
No.No way.
大卫的父亲可能是个混蛋，但他的政治立场很重要。
David's dad can be a dick, but his politics check out.
乔丹：伙计们……
Jordan: Guys...
这是什么鬼？
What the fuck is this?
呃……但是……
Uh...but...
他想为飓风做好准备。他...
He wanted to be prepared for the hurricane.He...
苏菲：他为什么要在他的他妈的地图上圈出他妈的房子？
Sophie: Why did he circle the fucking house
on his fucking map?
乔丹：我们必须在他之前找到艾玛。
Jordan: We have to find Emma before he does.
苏菲：好的。
Sophie: Okay.
乔丹：接下来让我们检查一下我的房间。
Jordan: Let's check my room next.
乔丹：我不认为他躲在我的胸罩里。
Jordan: I don't think he's hiding in my bra.
爱丽丝：伙计们……
Alice: Guys...
过来。
Come here.
哦，天哪，艾玛。
Oh, my god, Emma.
艾玛。
Emma.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
艾玛：发生了什么事？你们在做什么？
Emma: What's going on?What are you guys doing?
你吓到我怎么回事？
You scared me what's happening?
这里太热了。
It's so hot in here.
那是什么？
What is that?
Xanax. 你想要一个吗？是的，给我一个。
Xanax.Do you want one?Yeah, give me one.
你想要一个吗？ 苏菲：不。
You want one?Sophie: No.
乔丹：嘿，你拿着这个。
Jordan: Hey, you take this.
为什么？乔丹：我会找到格雷格的。
Why?Jordan: I'm gonna find Greg.
格雷格，为什么？麦克斯呢？
Greg, why?Where's Max?
也许是马克斯做到了。也许他在这里。
Maybe Max did it.Maybe he is here.
马克斯对大卫很生气。
Max was really angry at David.
我是认真的，
I'm serious, he looked like he was gonna
他看起来像是要做一些非常糟糕的事情。
do something really fucked up.
乔丹：爱丽丝！闭嘴。我只是说。
Jordan: Alice!Shut up.I'm just saying.
麦克斯永远不会。
Max would never.
我们去找格雷格吧。
Let's go find Greg.
好的。
Okay.
乔丹：什么...
Jordan: What the...
什么鬼？爱丽丝：哦，我的上帝。
What the fuck?Alice: Oh, my god.
苏菲：他脸上到底是什么鬼？
Sophie: What the hell is on his face?
这是他的光疗面具。他患有季节性抑郁症。
It's his light therapy mask.He has seasonal depression.
乔丹：我们走吧。
Jordan: Let's go.
嘿……嘘……
Hey...shh...
爱丽丝：格雷格。
Alice: Greg.
怎么了？ 乔丹：你去哪儿了？
What's up?Jordan: Where have you been?
嗯？
Huh?
你去哪儿了？
Where have you been?
哦，我，呃...
Oh, I, uh...
我睡不着，
I couldn't sleep,
所以我下来这里锻炼身体。
so I came down here to do my exercises.
爱丽丝：你为什么不回答我？
Alice: Why didn't you answer me?
你是在呼唤我吗？
Were you calling for me?
爱丽丝：是的。
Alice: Yeah.
我……我戴着耳机。
I...I had my headphones in.
你们还在玩狼人吗？
Are you guys still playing werewolf?
爱丽丝：格雷格！
Alice: Greg!
停！停！
Stop!Stop it!
好的。
All right.
我该怎么办，嗯？
What am I supposed to do, huh?
你为什么不告诉我们，该死的格雷格？
Why don't you tell us, fucking Greg?
格雷格：那是我的手提包吗？那是刀吗？
Greg: Is that my go bag?Is that a knife?
你为什么带了一个围棋包？
Why did you bring a go bag?
飓风？看，我告诉过你。
The hurricane?See, I told you.
苏菲：你为什么要在你他妈的地图上圈出他妈的房子？
Sophie: Why did you circle the fucking house
on your fucking map?
发生了什么事？大卫死了。
What's going on?David is dead.
他的身体在外面。
His body is outside.
大卫的尸体。等等，什么？
David's body.Wait, what?
你为什么要杀大卫？
Why did you kill David?
你杀了我男朋友
You murdered my boyfriend.
不，不。大卫杀了我。对吧？
No, no.David killed me.Right?
乔丹：这不是开玩笑，格雷格。
Jordan: This isn't a joke, Greg.
大卫死了。有人割开了他的喉咙。
David is dead.Somebody slit his throat.
什么？ 苏菲：用他妈的剑，
What?Sophie: With a fucking sword,
你他妈的病了！
you fucking sick fuck!
哦...
Oh...
你们在和我混吗？
You guys are fucking with me?
哦，你们在和我开玩笑。
Oh, you guys are fucking with me.
他妈的！
Fuck!
可爱的。
Cute.
不！
No!
好的。
Okay.
每个人都需要深呼吸。
Everyone needs to take a deep breath.
爱丽丝。
Alice.
苏菲：把我的刀还给我！
Sophie: Give me my knife back!
到底是怎么回事？
What the fuck is going on?
我不知道！
I don't know!
放下武器。 乔丹：你放下它。
Put down the weapons.Jordan: You put it down.
现在！
Now!
在地上！
On the floor!
乔丹：好的，好的。这个怎么样？
Jordan: Okay, okay.How about this?
放下它。 乔丹：好的，好的，好的。
Put it down.Jordan: Okay, okay, okay.
好的，我们会把它们放下。
Okay, we'll put them down.
我们会放……我们都会放下它们。
We'll put...we'll all put them down.
对吧？如果你放下你的，我们就会放下它们。
Right?We'll put them down if you put yours down.
我们会把它们放下。
We'll put them down.
好的。
Okay.
好的，请，请。
Okay.Yeah, please, please.
这似乎是公平的。爱丽丝：是的。
That seems fair.Alice: Yeah.
好的。
Okay.
放下它。
Putting it down.
我们很好。是的。
We're good.Yeah.
好的，这很好。
Okay, this is good.
好的。
All right.
乔丹！你还好吗？
Jordan!Are you okay?
噢！爱丽丝：停！停！
Ow!Alice: Stop!Stop!
请停下！格雷格：爱丽丝？
Please stop!Greg: Alice?
爱丽丝：停，停！
Alice: Stop.Stop!
不，不！
No!No!
苏菲！不，不，不，不，苏菲！
Sophie!No.No, no, no, Sophie!
格雷格：妈的。
Greg: Mother fucker.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
爱丽丝：这是不对的。
Alice: This isn't right.
他没有这样做。
He didn't do it.
爱丽丝，你怎么知道？你怎么知道他知道的？
Alice, how do you know?How do you that know he did?
看，我的意思是，就像...
Look, I mean, like...
如果你从逻辑上看我们所有人，
If you look at all of us, like,
就像在纸面上，
on paper, logically,
他是最有可能犯下暴力行为的。
he is the most likely to commit an act of violence.
在纸上？
On paper?
你他妈在说什么？
What the fuck are you even talking about?
我的意思是，他是唯一一个在军
队服役的人，对吧？所以...
I mean, he's the only one
我的意思是，他是唯一一个在军
队服役的人，对吧？所以...
who served in the military, right?So...
什么？
What?
乔丹：他是一名兽医。
Jordan: He's a vet.
对吗？像伊拉克一样？或者...
Right?Like Iraq?Or...
艾玛：不，我以为是阿富汗。
Emma: No, I thought it was Afghanistan.
他是一名兽医。
He was a veterinarian.
他是兽医的助手。
He was a veterinarian's assistant.
你他妈现在是认真的吗？
Are you fucking serious right now?
艾玛：那你为什么叫他g.I.Joe？
Emma: Then why did you call him g.I.Joe?
因为……你见过他吗？
Because...have you seen him?
好吧，无论如何，无论哪种方式，就像
在我们所有人中，他是最大的未知数。
Well, regardless, either way,
好吧，无论如何，无论哪种方式，就像
在我们所有人中，他是最大的未知数。
like, out of all of us, he is the biggest unknown.
我们已经认识了一辈子。
We've known each other forever.
爱丽丝：乔丹，你想做什么？
Alice: Jordan, what are you trying to do?
乔丹：我不是……我不想做任何事情。
Jordan: I'm not...I'm not trying to do anything.
爱丽丝：他死了，好吗？
Alice: He's dead, okay?
他死了，我们杀了他。
He's dead.We killed him.
她杀了他。
She killed him.
去换你的衬衫。
Go change your shirt.
艾玛：我们需要离开。我们需要离开这里。
Emma: We need to leave.We need to get out of here.
我们没有车。
We don't have a car.
好的，我要走路了。艾玛，停下。
Okay, I'm going to walk.Emma, stop.
你什么意思？你不能他妈的...
What do you mean?You can't just fucking...
乔丹：艾玛，你简直就是在茫茫荒野中。
Jordan: Emma, you're literally in the middle of nowhere.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
爱丽丝：我的意思是，它可能是我们中的任何一个。
Alice: I mean, it could have been any of us.
熄灯后我们都散了。
We all scattered when the lights went out.
我的意思是，可能是麦克斯，好吗？
I mean, it could have been Max, okay?
爱丽丝，你不知道你在说什么。
Alice, you don't know what you are talking about.
因为你，他打了大卫的脸。
He punched David in the face because of you.
仅仅因为麦克斯爱上我并不意味着他会杀了大卫。
Just because Max is in love with me
doesn't mean he would kill David.
哦，你他妈怎么了？
Oh, what the fuck is wrong with you?
艾玛：什么？
Emma: What?
这不是关于你和麦克斯的。
This is not about you and Max.
你为什么这么刻薄？
Why are you being so mean?
因为我不高兴，艾玛。
Because I'm upset, Emma.
我很沮丧，因为有人杀了我最好的朋友。
I'm upset because somebody killed my best friend.
苏菲，你用过吗？我相信你在做
Sophie, did you use?I can believe you're making
这是关于你的。
this about you.
我也很难过，好吗？我也很害怕。
I'm sad, too, okay?I'm scared, too.
我非常爱他。
I loved him so much.
看起来不像。
It didn't seem like it.
什么？ 苏菲：看起来像
What?Sophie: It seemed like
你喜欢有男朋友。
you loved having a boyfriend.
你喜欢感觉舒适。
And you loved feeling comfortable.
但是，不，你不爱他。
But, no, you did not love him.
你他妈根本就不喜欢他。
You didn't even fucking like him.
你只是太害怕做任何事情。
You were just too scared to do anything about it.
所以你多呆了三年，
So you stayed for three years longer than you should have
因为你是个懦夫。
because you're a coward.
不，我不是。
No, I'm not.
我不是。
I'm not.
我不是。对吧？我...
I'm not.Right?I...
你……你太毒了。
You're...you're so toxic.
艾玛，冷静下来。你是。
Emma, calm down.You are.
不！不，我不会...
No!No, I'm not gonna...
你太毒了
You are so toxic.
老实说，当你从地球上掉下来时，大卫松了一口气。
And, honestly, when you fell off the face of the earth,
David was relieved.
他松了口气，不用再和你打交道了。
He was relieved he didn't have to deal with you anymore.
我真希望他们砍掉你的头，
I wish they had chopped off your head instead,
你这个没骨气的狗屎。
you spineless piece of shit.
苏菲。
Sophie.
爱丽丝： 真他妈的基督。
Alice: Jesus fucking Christ.
艾玛。
Emma.
艾玛，来吧，等等。
Emma, come on.Wait.
等等。爱丽丝：艾玛。
Wait.Alice: Emma.
艾玛。
Emma.
乔丹：那真是太好了，索夫。
Jordan: That was real nice, soph.
伙计们...
Guys...
蜜蜂在哪里？
Where the fuck is bee?
苏菲：艾玛。
Sophie: Emma.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉。
I'm really sorry.
我现在好操蛋。
I'm so fucked up right now.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
对不起，对不起。
I'm sorry.I'm sorry.
好吧？只是，就像，事情开始了……
Okay?It was just, like, things started coming...
这不是你想要的吗？
Isn't that what you wanted?
是的，艾玛，这就是我想要的。
Yeah, Emma, that's what I wanted.
这就是我的心情。
That's what I was in the mood for.
非常感谢。什么鬼？
Thank you very much.What the fuck?
耶稣基督！
Jesus Christ!
你总是认为每个人都爱你。
You always think everyone is in love with you.
太疯狂了，我...
It's so crazy.I...
对不起。
I'm sorry.
你想要这个吗？
Do you want this?
是的。
Yeah.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
当然。
Sure.
爱丽丝：蜜蜂？
Alice: Bee?
苏？
Soph?
乔丹：艾玛？
Jordan: Emma?
帮助！
Help!
约旦！
Jordan!
帮助！
Help!
Help.Jordan：你在哪里？
Help.Jordan: Where are you?
帮助！请，帮助！帮助！
Help!Please, help!Help!
救命！救命！救命！
Help!Help!Help!
艾玛。
Emma.
乔丹：哦，天哪。爱丽丝：艾玛。
Jordan: Oh, my god.Alice: Emma.
哦，我的上帝。哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my god.Oh, my god.
发生了什么事？我不知道！
What happened?I don't know!
我不知道。
I don't know.
不要碰她！我只是想...
Don't touch her!I'm just trying to...
不要。不！弄清楚发生了什么。
Don't.No!Figure out what happened.
乔丹：我不碰她怎么知道？
Jordan: How am I supposed to know if I don't touch her?
爱丽丝：不要，不要，不要。
Alice: Don't, just don't, just don't.
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
爱丽丝：我听到了什么。
Alice: I heard something.
嗯，也许她...
Um, maybe she...
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
她摔倒了，也许她绊倒了？爱丽丝：没有。
She fell, maybe she tripped?Alice: No.
不，不，她……
No, no.She...
她……她被推了，好吗？
She...she got pushed, okay?
她被推了。我告诉过你这不是格雷格！
She was pushed.I told you it wasn't Greg!
乔丹：她死了，你高兴吗？
Jordan: Are you happy that she's dead?
不，但我告诉过你这不是格雷格！
No, but I told you it wasn't Greg!
我做了……我确实告诉过你。
I did...I did tell you.
爱丽丝：你没看到发生了什么吗？
Alice: Don't you see what's happening?
什么？
What?
谁是凶手？
Who was the killer?
什么？
What?
谁是凶手？
Who was the killer?
在游戏里？
In the game?
它遵循相同的模式。
It's following the same pattern.
死亡。
The deaths.
拜托……拜托，别说话了，拜托！
Please...please, just stop talking, please!
大卫、格雷格、艾玛。
David, Greg, Emma.
乔丹：不，是的！
Jordan: No.Yes!
他妈的是的，乔丹！乔丹：不。
Fucking yes, Jordan!Jordan: No.
不，它没有遵循相同的模式。
No, it's not following the same pattern.
格雷格死了，然后我们处决了大卫。
Greg died and then we executed David.
但在现实生活中，大卫死了，然后我们...
But in real life, David died and then we...
好的，但是格雷格，大卫，艾玛。格雷格，大卫，艾玛。
Okay, but Greg, David, Emma.Greg, David, Emma.
我的意思是，除非他们想让我们找到她
，否则为什么会有人把她留在那里？
I mean, why else would somebody leave her there
我的意思是，除非他们想让我们找到她
，否则为什么会有人把她留在那里？
unless they wanted us to find her?
他们为什么要我们找到她？
Why would they want us to find her?
因为他们在玩一个恶心的他妈的游戏。
Because they're playing a sick fucking game.
好的？
Okay?
谁是凶手？我不是凶手。
Who was the killer?I wasn't the killer.
爱丽丝，你他妈被烧焦了。
Alice, you're fucking coked out.
你被烧焦了，好吗？我们都被烧焦了。
You're coked out, okay?We're all coked out.
我不是。
I'm not.
你化妆了吗？
Are you wearing make up?
我……我在楼上，换我的……
I...I was upstairs, changing my...
爱丽丝：你看起来很奇怪。
Alice: You look weird.
这是谁的毛衣？
Whose sweater is this?
我在楼上找到的。
I found it upstairs.
你认识她多久了？
How long have you known her?
停下，爱丽丝。
Stop, Alice.
你是谁？
Who are you?
什么？你出现在这里，
What?You show up here,
开始对我的男朋友微笑。
start smiling at my boyfriend.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
你的声音在颤抖。
Your voice is trembling.
不不不，是的。
No.No.Yeah.It is.
乔丹：我用谷歌搜索了你。
Jordan: I googled you.
今年从犹他州毕业的人中没有一个叫你名字的人。
And there was nobody with your name
who graduated from Utah state this year.
根本没有你出席的记录。
There's literally no record of your attendance, at all.
什么鬼？
What the fuck?
听着，我可以解释。
Listen, I can explain.
爱丽丝：哦，天哪。
Alice: Oh, my god.
你发现了大卫的尸体。
You discovered David's body.
不，我只是……你本可以篡改
No, I just...You could have tampered
用发电机，
with the generator,
就像你篡改了索菲的车一样。
just like you tampered with Sophie's car.
你说你没关灯，对吧？
You said you left the lights on, right?
你是认真的吗？我们看着你杀人。
Are you serious?We watched you kill someone.
你真的谋杀了格雷格！
You literally murdered Greg!
字面上地！
Literally!
从字面上看！你他妈的该死！
Literally!You sick fuck!
不，你疯了吗？不，冷静点。
No, are you crazy?No.Calm down.
让我们谈谈它。谈谈它？
Let's just talk about it.Talk about it?
蜜蜂：是的。不……不。
Bee: Yeah.No...no.
蜜蜂：让我们谈谈吧，好吗？
Bee: Let's just talk about it, okay?
嗯，嗯，我不想。
Mmm-mmm.I don't want to.
蜜蜂：苏菲……苏菲。爱丽丝：不！
Bee: Sophie...Sophie.Alice: No!
Bee：Sophie.Ali，ce：别碰她！
Bee: Sophie.Ali, ce: Do not touch her!
哇！
Whoa!
爱丽丝：你知道吗？我不...
Alice: You know what?I don't...
我不想让你在这里。
I don't want you in here.
好吧，冷静点。
Okay, calm down.
不，说真的。爱丽丝！
No, seriously.Alice!
爱丽丝！我不要你在这里。
Alice!I don't want you in here.
蜜蜂：我……放松。闭嘴！闭嘴！
Bee: I...relax.Just shut up!Shut up!
我不想让你在这里。
I don't want you in here.
离开这个房间！放开我，爱丽丝。
Get out of this room!Let go of me, Alice.
滚出这个房间！
Get the fuck out of this room!
我不想再看你的脸了。出去。
I don't want to look at your face anymore.Get out.
蜜蜂：爱丽丝，冷静点。爱丽丝：我不是……
Bee: Alice, calm down.Alice: I'm not...
爱丽丝：我没有冷静下来。蜜蜂：放开我，爱丽丝。
Alice: I'm not calming down.Bee: Let go of me, Alice.
不，你杀了我他妈的男朋友。
No, you killed my fucking boyfriend.
你知道吗？你知道吗？这是自卫。
You know what?You know what?It was self-defense.
爱丽丝：我……我要她出去。
Alice: I...I want her out.
乔丹，你能帮帮我吗？好吧。
Jordan, can you help me?All right.
乔丹！耶稣，爱丽丝。
Jordan!Jesus, Alice.
去他妈的门！
Get the fucking door!
耶稣他妈的基督！
Jesus fucking Christ!
我不要她在这里！
I do not want her in here!
蜜蜂：放松！爱丽丝：不！
Bee: Relax!Alice: No!
苏菲！苏菲，做点什么！
Sophie!Sophie, do something!
你杀了他，滚！
You killed him, get out!
苏菲！爱丽丝：出去！
Sophie!Alice: Get out!
苏菲！
Sophie!
乔丹：待在这里。
Jordan: Stay here.
爱丽丝：我好饿。
Alice: I'm so hungry.
乔丹：你现在怎么会饿？
Jordan: How can you be hungry right now?
爱丽丝：我没有这个打算。
Alice: I wasn't planning on this.
乔丹：爱丽丝……
Jordan: Alice...
什么鬼？你他妈怎么进来的？
What the fuck?How the fuck you get in here?
她有枪。
She has a gun.
乔丹口袋里有枪，苏菲，离她远点。
Jordan has a gun in her pocket, Sophie,
get away from her.
不，不，苏菲，她很困惑……
No, no, Sophie, she's confusing...
让我走。
Let go of me.
你在开玩笑吧？
Are you kidding me?
我没有枪。
I don't have a gun.
蜜蜂：那就清空你的口袋。
Bee: Then empty your pockets.
慢慢来！
Slowly!
而已？
That's it?
而已。
That's it.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
你是凶手。
You are the killer.
在……在游戏中……我……
In the...in the game...I...
你他妈怎么进来的？
How the fuck did you get in here?
枪在哪里？我他妈的没有枪。
Where is the gun?I don't have a fucking gun.
我们把所有的门都锁上了。你是怎么进来的？
We locked all the doors.How did you get in?
你杀了他。
You killed him.
我为什么要杀大卫？我为什么要杀大卫？
Why would I kill David?Why would I kill David?
我为什么要杀艾玛？
Why would I kill Emma?
从字面上看，他们是我最老的朋友。
They are, literally, my oldest friends.
你他妈就是见了他们！你怎么敢？
You just fucking met them!How dare you?
当我找到大卫时，
When I found David,
你是最后一个到达那里的人。
you were the last person to get there.
你花了一点时间。这是真的。
It took you awhile.That's true.
蜜蜂：艾玛死的时候你在哪里，嗯？
Bee: Where were you when Emma died, hmm?
你推她！闭嘴！
You pushed her!Shut up!
伙计们，别听她的。你他妈不知道
Guy's, don't listen to her.You don't know what the fuck
你在谈论！然后，我看到了你。
you're talking about!And then, I saw you.
我看见你拿枪了。
I saw you getting the gun.
乔丹：那是谎言。
Jordan: That's a lie.
那是他妈的谎言。你在撒谎。你是个骗子！
That's a fucking lie.You're lying.You're a liar!
你在用你他妈的牙齿撒谎。
You're lying through your fucking teeth.
你对一切都撒了谎。
You lied about everything.
你对苏菲撒了谎。
You lied about everything to Sophie.
你他妈的是个骗子。
You're a fucking liar.
是的，你……你确实对苏菲撒了谎。
Yeah, you...You did lie to Sophie.
好的。
Okay.
我确实去了犹他州一个学期。
I did go to Utah state
for one semester.
但我妈妈……她过得很艰难
But my mom was...She was having a hard time
我回家照顾她。
and I came home to take care of her.
我确实在gamehut工作，但他们关闭了
我们的位置，就像我认识你一周后。我...
...我一直在申请，但是......
And I did work at gamehut,
我确实在gamehut工作，但他们关闭了
我们的位置，就像我认识你一周后。我...
...我一直在申请，但是......
but they shut down our location, like,
我确实在gamehut工作，但他们关闭了
我们的位置，就像我认识你一周后。我...
...我一直在申请，但是......
a week after I met you.I...I've been applying, but...
我把你送到商场的时候你在做什么？
What were you doing when I dropped
you off at the mall?
在美食广场闲逛。我...
Hung out at the food court.I...
不想让你失望。
Didn't want to disappoint you.
我很不好意思。
I was embarrassed.
我应该告诉你的。我只是...
I should have told you.I just...
我的妈妈，她...
My mom, she...
她有...
She has...
我妈妈有边缘。
My mom has borderline.
爱丽丝：哦，天哪。
Alice: Oh, my god.
很抱歉，那是...
I'm so sorry, that's...
这真的很严重。
That's really serious.
心理健康是一个非常严重的问题。
Mental health is a really serious issue.
我的意思是，我从来没有对任何人说过这句话，但是...
I mean, I've never actually said this to anyone, but...
但我有身体畸形。
But I have body dysmorphia.
哦，我的上帝。闭嘴，爱丽丝。
Oh, my god.Shut the fuck up, Alice.
我想告诉你。我只是...
I wanted to tell you.I just...
我只是真的希望你喜欢我。
I just really wanted you to like me.
你他妈一定是在开玩笑。
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
乔丹，什么鬼？
Jordan, what the fuck?
你是在告诉我你相信那一堆废话吗？
Are you telling me that you believe that
pile of bullshit?
这应该激发信心吗？
Is that supposed to inspire confidence?
她妈妈有“边界”。
Her mom has "borderline."
这对其他人来说不是一个他妈的红旗吗？
Is that not a red fucking flag to anybody else?
这是一个严重的问题。
That's a serious issue.
你他妈从哪儿弄来的？
Where the fuck did you get that?
大卫的爸爸很有钱！
David's dad's rich!
有钱人有他妈的枪，苏菲！
Rich people have fucking guns, Sophie!
我父母很有钱，他们没有枪。
My parents are rich.They don't have guns.
好吧，我的意思是，我们都很有钱
，但你和大卫都很有钱，很有钱。
Well, I mean, we're all rich,
好吧，我的意思是，我们都很有钱
，但你和大卫都很有钱，很有钱。
but you and David are like rich, rich.
这对我来说从来都不重要...
That has never mattered to me...
哦，他妈的闭嘴！
Oh, shut the fuck up!
我们甚至不想邀请你。
We didn't even want to invite you.
我们讨论过邀请你，
We debated about inviting you,
但因为这是大卫的家。
but because it's David's house.
我没这么说，但是...
I didn't say that, but...
而且，不，您没有在群聊中回复。
And, no, you did not respond in the group chat.
然后，你和这个该死的精神病患者一起出现。
And then, you show up with this fucking psychopath.
不要称她为精神病患者，那太能干了。
Don't call her a psychopath, that's so ableist.
操你妈，你们值得彼此。
Fuck you.You deserve each other.
我希望她他妈的让你在睡梦中窒息。
I hope she fucking suffocates you in your sleep.
爱丽丝：是的，你没有在聊天中回复。
Alice: Yeah, you didn't reply in the chat.
大卫实际上告诉我，
And David actually told me
你请求他和你的父母谈谈，
that you, like, begged him to talk to your parents
然后再次解除你的信任。
and, like, unlock your trust again.
这就是为什么你真的在这里。
And that's why you're actually here.
哦耶？
Oh, yeah?
哦，是的，他有没有告诉过你，
当你们在我面前围着栏杆时。
Oh, yeah, did he tell you that
哦，是的，他有没有告诉过你，
当你们在我面前围着栏杆时。
while you guys were railing lines in front of me.
你应该如此担心的瘾君子朋友？
Your addict friend
who you're supposedly so worried about?
我们很担心。 苏菲：不！
We are worried.Sophie: No!
不，不，不。让我直说。
No, no, no.Let me get this straight.
好吧，让我直说吧。
Okay, let me get this straight.
所以，当黑人女孩有可乐的习惯时，这是一个问题。
So, when the black girl
has a coke habit, it's a problem.
但是当她周围的其他人都这样做时，
But when everyone else around her does it,
包括她最好的朋友，
including her best friend, who happens to be white
他恰好是白人和男性，
and male,
这很好吗？
it's fine?
我理解，
I understand and I'm an ally,
我是盟友，
and I totally get how it...
看起来是这样的。
Looks that way.
和...
And...
嗯...
Um...
乔丹？哦，天哪。
Jordan?Oh, my god.
你沉迷于扮演受害者。
You are obsessed with playing the victim.
苏菲：对不起？
Sophie: Excuse me?
我不得不和你一起坐救护车三次，
I had to ride in the ambulance with you
以为你已经死了。
three times, thinking you were dead.
我需要帮助，我得到了，我很抱歉。你有帮助吗？
I needed help and I got it
and I'm sorry.You got help?
你的意思是，我们不得不向你他妈的老爸
告诫，这样他就会切断你的联系，把你送
去康复中心，而你却真的是在踢和尖叫。
You mean we had to narc on you to your fucking dad
你的意思是，我们不得不向你他妈的老爸
告诫，这样他就会切断你的联系，把你送
去康复中心，而你却真的是在踢和尖叫。
so he'd cut you off and ship you off to rehab,
你的意思是，我们不得不向你他妈的老爸
告诫，这样他就会切断你的联系，把你送
去康复中心，而你却真的是在踢和尖叫。
while you were quite literally kicking and screaming.
是的，然后你就
Yeah.And then you just
从地球表面掉下来。
fell off the face of the earth.
因为这就是你所做的，苏菲。
'Cause that's what you do, soph.
当事情变得艰难时，这就是你所做的，你跑。
That's what you do when things get tough, you run.
你跑去写你他妈的回忆录。
You ran away to go write your fucking memoirs.
这是创造性的非小说，
It's creative non-fiction which is a valid response
是对注意力经济中生活的有效回应。
to life in an attention economy.
哦，滚蛋，死吧。
Oh, fuck off and die.
你写一些关于你妈妈和她的伏特加的小文章。
You write little essays
about your mommy and her vodka.
还有你的阴户和你的感受。
And your pussy and your feelings.
还有你他妈的感情。
And your fucking feelings.
哦，我的上帝，我们都沉浸在你他妈的感情中。
Oh, my god, we are all drowning
in your fucking feelings.
感觉是事实。不！不，它们不是。
Feelings are facts.No!No, they're not.
事实就是事实。
Facts are facts.
苏菲，你为什么要捉弄我们？
Why did you ghost us, Sophie?
比如为什么？
Like why?
因为你他妈的触发了我。
Because you fucking trigger me.
你使我。
You enable me.
她知道吗？
Does she know?
苏菲：她知道吗？
Sophie: Does she know what?
你求我在我来这里的路上停在你的公寓。
That you begged me
to stop at your apartment on my way up here.
我做到了。
And I did.
我们上了你的车。
And we fucked in your car.
她他妈在撒谎。
She's fucking lying.
她用她他妈的牙齿撒谎。
She's lying through her fucking teeth.
她正试图进入你的脑海。
She's trying to get in your head.
别听她的，好吗？
Don't listen to her, okay?
检查她的文字。
Check her texts.
你疯了，乔丹。
You are unhinged, Jordan.
你缺乏同理心。
You are devoid of empathy.
你没有感觉。
You have no feelings.
你想知道为什么我永远不能和你在一起吗？
Do you want to know why I could never
ever be with you?
因为你在你他妈的谷歌日历上安排了一切，包括性。
Because you schedule
everything in your fucking Google calendar,
因为你在你他妈的谷歌日历上安排了一切，包括性。
including sex.
因为你没有灵魂。
Because you have no soul.
乔丹：去你妈的。
Jordan: Fuck you.
你在情感上虐待。
You're emotionally abusive.
我不得不去治疗创伤后应激障碍。
I had to go to therapy for PTSD.
你他妈的可以问爱丽丝。
You can fucking ask Alice.
是的，她做到了。
Yeah, she did.
需很长时间。
For a long time.
你讨厌爱丽丝。
You hate Alice.
不，我没有。是的，你鄙视她。
No, I don't.Yeah, you despise her.
你不断抱怨她是多么的乏味和烦人。
You complain constantly about how vapid
你讨厌她。
and annoying she is.You hate her.
可惜你不停地取笑她愚蠢的小播客。
It's pitiful how you won't stop making fun
of her stupid little podcast.
让她有播客。
Let her have the podcast.
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're talking about.
你讨厌听她的播客。
You hate listen to her podcast.
等待...
Wait...
什么？
What?
你让我们发誓不告诉任何人。
And you made us swear on our lives
not to tell anyone.
乔丹，这是真的吗？
Jordan, is that true?
我喜欢你的播客，爱丽丝。
I like your podcast, Alice.
你的播客是关于什么的？
What is your podcast about?
和你最聪明、最有趣的朋友一起出去玩。
Hanging out with your smartest and funniest friend.
你只是呻吟吗？
Did you just groan?
不。
No.
当我说和你最聪明、最有趣的朋友“闲逛”时。”
When I said "hanging out
"with your smartest and funniest friend."
哦，我的上帝。像那样。像那样！
Oh, my god.Like that.Like that!
操！你又做了一次。
Fuck!You just did it again.
不，我没有！首先，
No, I didn't!First of all,
播客需要做很多工作，好吗？
a podcast takes a lot of work, okay?
你必须组织客人。
You have to organize the guests.
你必须做一个谷歌日历，
You have to do a Google calendar
然后建立一个追随者。
and you build a following.
这他妈的需要很长时间！
It takes a long fucking time!
而且我已经为此工作了一段时间！
And I've been working on it for a while!
好的？
Okay?
然后，让我说，没有人喜欢你，好吗？
And then, let me say,
that nobody likes you, okay?
没人喜欢你！没人喜欢你！
Nobody likes you!Nobody likes you!
你知道当你喝醉了，你对我哭泣，“哦，我怕没人
喜欢我”，因为我很卑鄙，是个婊子，我很烂。
Do you know when you're drunk and you cry to me,
你知道当你喝醉了，你对我哭泣，“哦，我怕没人
喜欢我”，因为我很卑鄙，是个婊子，我很烂。
"oh, I'm afraid nobody likes me
你知道当你喝醉了，你对我哭泣，“哦，我怕没人
喜欢我”，因为我很卑鄙，是个婊子，我很烂。
"because I'm mean and a bitch and I suck."
好吧，你知道，好吗？你他妈的太烂了。
Well, you do, okay?You fucking suck.
我只是出于同情和我们共同历史的
令人窒息的重量和你一起出去玩。
And I only hang out with you out of pity
我只是出于同情和我们共同历史的
令人窒息的重量和你一起出去玩。
and the suffocating weight of our shared history.
仅此而已。
And that is all.
而且你就是那么爱你白手起家的故事，就像你
是世界上唯一一个不是来自金钱的他妈的人。
And you're just so in love
而且你就是那么爱你白手起家的故事，就像你
是世界上唯一一个不是来自金钱的他妈的人。
with your rags to riches narrative,
而且你就是那么爱你白手起家的故事，就像你
是世界上唯一一个不是来自金钱的他妈的人。
like you're the only fucking person in the world
而且你就是那么爱你白手起家的故事，就像你
是世界上唯一一个不是来自金钱的他妈的人。
who didn't come from money.
你知道吗？
You know what?
你的父母是中产阶级。
Your parents are upper middle class.
不，他们不是。
No, they're not.
约旦。
Jordan.
他们是。
They are.
他们在一所大学任教。
They teach at a university.
是公开的。
It's public.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
哦，我的上帝，我的意思是，难怪索菲会奇怪。
Oh, my god, I mean, no wonder Sophie od'd.
谁能与优越情结的他妈的电子表格约会？
Who could date a fucking spreadsheet
with a superiority complex?
就像，你是这样一个...
It's, like, you're such a...
哦！
Ow!
什么鬼？
What the fuck?
苏菲：他妈的，乔丹？
Sophie: What the fuck, Jordan?
爱丽丝：哦，天哪，你是认真的吗？
Alice: Oh, my god.Are you serious?
你他妈是不是直接开枪打我了？
Did you just fucking shoot me?
不，爱丽丝：你他妈的朝我开枪。
No.Alice: You fucking shot me.
用枪！
With a gun!
乔丹：不，我没有开枪打你。我……
Jordan: No, I didn't shoot you.I...
爱丽丝：你他妈谋杀了他们，你这个怪物！
Alice: You fucking murdered them, you freak!
你是凶手，我就知道！
You're the murderer.I knew it!
我就知道，你真是个婊子！
I knew it, you're such a bitch!
你真是个他妈的婊子！
You're such a fucking bitch!
我没有谋杀任何人。爱丽丝：是的，你做到了。
I didn't murder anybody.Alice: Yes, you did.
乔丹，放下枪。
Jordan, put the gun down.
爱丽丝：我以前从未被枪杀过。
Alice: I've never been shot before.
真他妈疼！
It really fucking hurts!
索菲：请把那该死的枪放下。
Sophie: Put the fucking gun down, please.
你做到了。你让我做到了。
You did this.You made me do this.
你为什么让我这样做？
Why did you make me do that?
你在做什么？放下枪。
What are you doing?Put the gun down.
为什么？你为什么开枪打我？
Why?Why did you shoot me?
乔丹：我没有射你。
Jordan: I did not shoot you.
是的，你做到了！用那把枪！停，停，停。
Yes, you did!With that gun!Stop, stop, stop.
爱丽丝，停下。停下！用那把枪。
Alice, stop.Stop!With that gun.
别再挥手了，我不会挥手的。
Stop waving it around.I'm not waving.
别打我，你已经开枪了。
Don't hit me.You already shot me.
停下！别碰我。
Stop!Don't touch me.
苏菲：不，不，不！爱丽丝：拿枪！
Sophie: No, no, no!Alice: Get the gun!
苏菲：不！爱丽丝：苏菲，枪！
Sophie: No!Alice: Sophie, the gun!
不要！停下！你在我的腿上！
Don't!Stop!You're on my leg!
你在我的腿上！
You're on my leg!
我要，给我！
I want it.Give it to me!
乔丹：不！ 苏菲：放手！
Jordan: No!Sophie: Let go!
乔丹：不！
Jordan: No!
苏菲：噢！
Sophie: Ow!
爱丽丝：不！
Alice: No!
不！爱丽丝：给我。
No!Alice: Give it to me.
给我！给我！放开我！不！
Give me it!Give me it!Get off of me!No!
乔丹：滚开我！
Jordan: Get the fuck off me!
下车！
Get off!
噢！我他妈的腿！
Ow!My fucking leg!
苏菲：在哪里？
Sophie: Where is it?
爱丽丝：噢！
Alice: Ow!
我没有这样做。
I didn't do it.
请不要动。
Please, don't move.
你他妈别动。
Don't you fucking move.
没关系……没关系，乔丹。
It's okay...It's okay, Jordan.
请不要这样做。
Please, don't do it.
请，只是...
Please, just...
停止！我没有这样做。请停止，好吗？
Stop!I didn't do it.Please, just stop, okay?
放下吧，求求你，别动了。
Just put it down.Please, stop moving.
拜托……拜托，请不要跟着我，拜托。
Please...please, don't follow me, please.
请...停止！停止！停止！
Please...Stop!Stop it!Stop it!
停，停，停！
Stop, stop, stop!
苏菲：我们为什么要这样做？
Sophie: Why are we doing this?
乔丹：别上来。
Jordan: Don't come up here.
不要，请，不要。
Don't, please, don't.
苏菲：请放下。
Sophie: Please put it down.
乔丹：请停下来。请留在那里。
Jordan: Please stop.Please stay there.
我的天啊。
Oh, my god.
苏菲：请……
Sophie: Please...
乔丹：停下。苏菲：我求求你了……
Jordan: Stop.Sophie: I'm begging you...
别他妈上这儿来拜托
Don't fucking come up here.Please.
苏菲，我是认真的，就呆在那里。
Sophie, I'm serious, just stay there.
苏菲：停下。
Sophie: Stop.
待在那里，请待在那里。
Just stay there.Just please stay there.
我求你。
I'm begging you.
请，他妈的...他妈的呆在那里！操！
Please, fucking...Fucking stay there!Fuck!
苏菲：蜜蜂！
Sophie: Bee!
检查她的文字。
Check her texts.
苏菲。
Sophie.
你杀了艾玛？
Did you kill Emma?
不。
No.
你是否？
Did you?
不。
No.
没关系，如果你做到了，没关系。
It's okay, if you did it.It's okay.
我只是想知道。你可以告诉我。
I just want to know.You can tell me.
你杀了大卫？什么？
Did you kill David?What?
不。
No.
你杀了格雷格。
You killed Greg.
为了保护你。
To protect you.
我不得不。
I had to.
你会诚实地回答这个问题吗？
Will you answer this honestly?
好的，我保证。那是什么？
Okay, I promise.What is it?
你是否...
Did you...
与乔丹？
With Jordan?
不。
No.
不，我没有……我没有。我永远不会。
No, I didn't...I didn't.I would never.
我爱你，好吗？
I love you, okay?
你爱我吗？
Do you love me?
我只是想触碰你。
I just wanted to touch you.
你吓到我了。
You frighten me.
苏菲：蜜蜂！
Sophie: Bee!
蜜蜂！
Bee!
我们必须在一起！
We have to stay together!
蜜蜂！
Bee!
蜜蜂？
Bee?
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我爱你。
I love you.
我们必须在一起。
We have to stay together.
蜜蜂！
Bee!
好的，蜜蜂！
Okay.Bee!
嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey.
我一直在到处寻找你。
I've been looking for you everywhere.
我得告诉你一件事。
I have to tell you something.
我去了爱丽丝的房间，我...
I went to Alice's room and I...
然后我找到了可乐然后...
And then I found coke and then...
我……我对艾玛和她说了所有这些话……
I...I said all these things to Emma and she...
我...我给她吃药是因为...
I...I gave her pills 'cause...
然后她绊倒了。
And then she tripped and fell.
我的错。
It's my fault.
苏菲，没关系，没关系。
Sophie, it's okay.It's okay.
苏菲：我以为没有人会相信我。
Sophie: I thought no one would believe me.
给我你的手机。
Give me your phone.
什么？
What?
我想看看你和乔丹的文字。
I want to see your text with Jordan.
不。
No.
我得看看你的文字。
I have to see your texts.
请？
Please?
苏菲：不，苏菲。
Sophie: No.Sophie.
苏菲：住手！
Sophie: Stop!
那不是我的电话。
That's not my phone.
啊什么？
Oh...what?
那不是我的电话。
That's not my phone.
♪ 好吧，我在屋子里很无聊，我在屋子里也很无聊。
♪ Okay, I'm bored in the house and I'm in the house bored.
♪ 在房子里无聊，我在房子里无聊。
♪ bored in the house and I'm in the house bored.
♪ 无聊的在家里无聊。
♪ bored in the motherfuckin' in the house bored.
我他妈的无聊。
♪ and I'm bored in the motherfuckin'.
在家里无聊。
♪ in the house bored.
♪ 在屋里无聊，在屋子里无聊。
♪ bored in the house, bored in the house bored.
我他妈的无聊。
♪ I'm bored in the motherfuckin'.
在家里无聊。
♪ in the house bored.
♪ 我他妈的无聊。♪ 在家里无聊，是的。
♪ and I'm bored in the motherfuckin'.
♪ in the house bored, aye.
♪ 我很无聊，我很无聊，我很无聊。
♪ I'm bored, I'm bored, I'm bored.
♪ 是的，我需要一个粗壮的小鸡。
♪ Aye, I need me a thick chicks.
♪ 坐在沙发上。
♪ sittin' on a couch.
♪ 我正在浏览我的 Netflix。
♪ and I'm going through my Netflix.
♪ 无聊的混蛋，我不是在做狗屎。
♪ bored in the motherfucker, I ain't doin' shit.
♪ 告诉她拉起来，让它像 nesquik 一样摇晃。
♪ tell her pull up, make it shake like nesquik.
♪ 脖子冻僵了，我们无处可去，婊子。
♪ neck frozen, we're nowhere to go, bitch.
♪ 像冰箱门一样告诉婊子寒意。
♪ Tell the bitch chill like refrigerator doors.
♪ 我们可以加热一些拉面。
♪ we can heat up some ramen.
♪ 不能去商店。
♪ can't go to the store.
♪ 甚至不能去巡演一个如此无聊的黑鬼 ♪。
♪ can't even go on tour a nigga so bored ♪.
发生了什么？
What happened?
我有接待。
I have reception.